<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.5.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://friendtainer.com/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://friendtainer.com/blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-07-01T10:50:40+02:00</updated><id>http://friendtainer.com/blog/</id><title type="html">Friendtainer Blog</title><subtitle>Honest advice about friendships and relationships.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">10 Easy Ways To Make Your Friendships Stronger</title><link href="http://friendtainer.com/blog/2017/06/29/ways-to-make-friendship-stronger/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="10 Easy Ways To Make Your Friendships Stronger" /><published>2017-06-29T14:23:00+02:00</published><updated>2017-06-29T14:23:00+02:00</updated><id>http://friendtainer.com/blog/2017/06/29/ways-to-make-friendship-stronger</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://friendtainer.com/blog/2017/06/29/ways-to-make-friendship-stronger/">&lt;h1&gt;10 Easy Ways To Make Your Friendships Stronger&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The true friendship is something beautiful and extremely valuable. It helps us develop as human beings and makes our lives more complete. However, if we want our friendship to &lt;strong&gt;stand the test of time&lt;/strong&gt; we have to take care of it no less than we care about love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below you can find 10 advices on how to make sure that your friendship won’t become weaker over time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;1. Be Loyal&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When talking to other people say only positive things about your friends. &lt;strong&gt;Never repeat things they told you &quot;in secrecy&quot;&lt;/strong&gt;. Be aware that one act of disloyalty can destroy even the strongest friendship. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;2. Be a Great Listener&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Listen to your friends even if you think that their problem is something irrelevant. If possible, you can try to change their point of you by &lt;strong&gt;showing the other perspectives&lt;/strong&gt; but be careful to do it in a gentle way. You can have different opinion that your friends but never ignore theirs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;3. Meet Friends Regularly&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course you can or even should call or text them. However, nothing can replace a face-to-face meeting. Therefore, even if you have a really busy time, try to find a moment to meet with your friends. You can use a special app such as &lt;a href=&quot;http://friendtainer.com&quot;&gt;Friendtainer&lt;/a&gt; which will help you meet your friends regularly. The benefit is that you don’t have to remember when you saw them the last time. &lt;a href=&quot;http://friendtainer.com&quot;&gt;Friendtainer&lt;/a&gt; will do it for you so you will earn more time to actually see them instead of spending it on planning the meetings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;4. Be Close To Them&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be close to them both in good and bad moments of their life. Even if you can’t help them to find a solution to their problems and objectively your presence doesn’t contribute too much. &lt;strong&gt;But they feel better knowing that there is a kindred spirit next to them.&lt;/strong&gt; And that’s your goal, isn’t it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;5. Forgive Them&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Forgive even if your friend did or said something that hurt you. Don’t be angry too long. You can be sure they didn’t make it on purpose. Also, if you have a fight, be the person who first gives hand to harmony and forgiveness. &lt;strong&gt;Don’t take offence.&lt;/strong&gt; The true friendship is worth of that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;6. Give Feedback&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t hide your feelings or opinion. You can give tell them if you don’t agree with them or disapprove their behaviour. While giving a feedback be always honest and constructive and try to finish with some positive quote, such as “I love you anyway”, or “But I like your shoes, they’re great” if you just said that that dress didn’t suit her figure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;7. Praise Them Often&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of us like receiving compliments, it just makes our day better. And it really doesn’t matter if other people praise our behaviour, achievements or look. Compliment is always positive, especially from a close person such a best friend. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;8. Don’t Be An Egoist&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be aware that you friend can have a partner, family, colleague or even other friends. So should you. &lt;strong&gt;You have to give your friend a space;&lt;/strong&gt; you can’t close them in a gold cage. Otherwise it just won’t work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;9. Be Responsible&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Provide advice if you see that your friend is doing something wrong, is overloaded with duties or their behaviour hurts other. &lt;strong&gt;Remember that you can only advise and it is up to your friend if they apply that or not.&lt;/strong&gt; Some people have to learn on their own mistakes and you can’t do much about it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;10. Don’t Be a Hero&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if you consider yourself as a stronger one in the relationship, you don’t have to be a hero all the time. Let your friend support you while having the worst time, share your secrets and problems with them. &lt;strong&gt;Accept their help and thank them for that.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Agnieszka Piechocka</name></author><summary type="html">10 Easy Ways To Make Your Friendships Stronger</summary></entry></feed>